(Sheldon:)What are you doing here?
(Stuart:)Um, Raj invited me to go to the movies
with you guys.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me, I didn't authorize this.
- Sheldon, you are not in charge.
- That's mighty sassy for a man...
(Sheldon:)...with a roommate performance review
around the corner.
(Raj:)What's the big deal?
You guys are bringing your girlfriends.
I didn't wanna sit by myself.
(Sheldon:)The big deal is, I was expecting us
to be an intimate group of five.
Now we're gonna be
a faceless mass of six.
(Leonard:)It'll be fine.
Just, uh, pretend he's Wolowitz.
(Sheldon:)Hmm...
(Sheldon:)- Do you like Raisinets?
- I take them or leave them.
(Sheldon:)At the movies,
Wolowitz always eats Raisinets.
(Stuart:)Would you feel more comfortable
if I ate Raisinets?
(Sheldon:)It's hardly my business what you eat.
(Sheldon:)As long as it doesn't crunch
during the film and it's Raisinets.
(Sheldon:)Okay.
(Stuart:)- Should we go?
- Uh, one more question.
If you're gonna replace Wolowitz,
I need to know a little more about you.